<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Rootkitty&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://rootkitty.tech/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Rootkitty&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:28:27 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rootkitty.tech/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Snipping Leak</title>
      <link>https://rootkitty.tech/post/snipping-leak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:28:27 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rootkitty.tech/post/snipping-leak/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that Windows inbuilt Snipping Tool leaks your user data? I didn&amp;rsquo;t but it came as quite a shock to discover.
JPEG Metadata So the JPEG file format provides methods of storing metadata about various things. Everything from GeoLocation to the Serial number of the Camera. All This data is stored as EXIF, and it can be quite verbose.
Those not paying attention to their metadata may soon find themselves leaking quite a lot of personal and identifiable data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Hugo</title>
      <link>https://rootkitty.tech/post/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 14:25:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rootkitty.tech/post/hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-hugo&#34;&gt;What is hugo?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; is a wonderful program written in &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/&#34;&gt;Golang&lt;/a&gt; to create static HTML from templates and markdown files. It&amp;rsquo;s fast, natively compiled, and does the job well.

It&amp;rsquo;s filled to the brim with features that I&amp;rsquo;m sure I won&amp;rsquo;t find any use for. It also has a plethora of themes that you can easily switch between.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://rootkitty.tech/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 05:17:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rootkitty.tech/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to my blog. This domain has beeen parked for some time while I attempted to find a nice blogging software, but I think found it.
Content Anyway, welcome to the blog I hope you enjoy it&amp;rsquo;s content. What content? Well none at this current time but it&amp;rsquo;ll essentially be a journal of all my escapades. Malware analysis, projects, and even just notes.
About me Enough about the blog, and more about me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>